Hey, what are you doing? Get off the computer.
Oye, ¿qué estás haciendo? Apaga la computadora.
I'm downloading a song.
Estoy descargando una canción.
Move your feet, lose your seat.
Mueve tus pies, pierde tu asiento.
What's the matter with you two?
¿Qué les pasa a ustedes dos?
Do you know how much this computer costs?
¿Sabes cuánto cuesta esta computadora?
You have the protection plan, right?
Tienes el plan de protección, ¿verdad?
I don't have the protection plan.
No tengo el plan de protección.
If I believed in protection plans, neither you would be here.
Si yo creyera en los planes de protección, tú no estarías aquí.
But you guys are spoiled brats. You take everything for granted.
Pero ustedes son niños mimados. Dan todo por sentado.
You guys wouldn't have been able to make it through one week of my childhood.
No habrían podido soportar ni una semana de mi infancia.
Oh, please. They wouldn't last one night at my house.
Oh, por favor. No durarían ni una noche en mi casa.
You know what? Let's do it.
¿Sabes qué? Hagámoslo.
You guys are spending the week at Grandma Benny's house.
Ustedes pasarán la semana en la casa de la abuela Benny.
What?
¿Qué?
I use your dad's old room for storage now.
Ahora uso la vieja habitación de tu papá para guardar cosas.
So you kids are gonna sleep on the pull-out couch.
Así que ustedes, niños, van a dormir en el sofá cama.
What time do we have to go to bed?
¿A qué hora tenemos que irnos a la cama?
I don't care. I got three basic rules.
No me importa. Tengo tres reglas básicas.
Don't drink my beer.
No bebas mi cerveza.
Don't touch my smokes.
No toques mis cigarros.
And don't sneak up on me when I'm sleeping.
Y no te me acerques a escondidas cuando estoy durmiendo.
I got a gun under my pillow.
Tengo una pistola debajo de la almohada.
And I sleep, oh, not your route.
Y duermo, oh, no tu ruta.